Lowell Thomas
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Lowell Thomas: Early friends and college days, circa 1905 - 1915; 6 (Box 1524)
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) on the far right with two women on a frozen lake], 30
    - [Group of people on a frozen lake], 31
    - [Three men standing outside of a house], 32
    - [Three men standing outside of a house], 33
    - [Three men standing outside of a house], 34
    - [Two men wrestling(?)], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas, center, with a man and woman on a porch], 36
    - [Young man], 37
    - [Three young men balanceing on saw horses (?), 38
    - [Three young men balanceing on saw horses (?), 39
    - [Group of youg men about to start a race, Lowell Thomas (?) with a starting pistol raised], 40
    - [Group of young men on the proch of a fraternity (?) Lowell Thomas on the right], 41
    - [Group of young people on a mountain top], 42
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) and a young woman], 43
    - [Group of young people sitting by a road], 44
    - [Three men with their kill], 45
    - [Four men branding a calf(?)], 46
  - Lowell Thomas: Early friends and college days, circa 1905 - 1915; 7 (Box 1524)
    - Age 18 - 1st year in college - Univ. of Northern Indiana [Valparaiso], 1
    - Note: Age 18 - 1st year in college - Univ. of Northern Indiana [Valparaiso], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) center with two other young men], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) reclining under a Sigma Gammas pendant], 4
    - [Skeleton on a couch with a beer stein, surrounded by memorabilia], 5
    - [Skeleton on a couch with a beer stein, surrounded by memorabilia], 6
    - [Man sitting on a chair reading a book, Sigma Gammas sign in the background], 7
    - [Young man sitting on a couch with pendants behind him], 8
    - [View of a mine (?)], 9
    - [Four women posing with a ball], 10
    - [Skeleton on a couch with a beer stein, surrounded by memorabilia], 11
    - [Young woman standing in front of a forest], 12
    - [Group of young men in front of '09 pendant], 13
    - [Group of young men, Lowell Thomas in the center (?)], 14
    - [Group of people sitting around a table, Lowell thomas in the center (?)], 15
    - [Group of 5 men sitting on a rocky hillside, Lowell Thomas middle right], 16
    - [Man in cap and gown with a beer stein in one hand and a book in the other], 17
    - [a group of young people posing on farm equipment (?)], 18
    - [Young man kicking a football], 19
    - [Two young men playing football], 20
    - [Young man and woman sitting together on a lawn], 21
    - [Two young men in football uniforms with another man], 22
    - [Young man in a football uniform, holding a football], 23
    - [Group of young men in a fraternity house (?) Lowell Thomas front right], 24
  - Lowell Thomas: Early friends and college days, circa 1905 - 1915; 8 (Box 1524)
    - Caption: J. J. Herold, C. B. Kennedy; Tacoma, Wn; 5/30/14, 1
    - [Two young man in football uniforms on a playing field], 2
    - [Three young men in baseball uniforms], 3
    - [Group of young people], 4
    - [Group of young men mock fighting], 5
    - [Young man standing on a train track], 6
    - [Group of young men posing on a train car], 7
    - [Train, steam engine (?), on a train track], 8
    - [group of men on a hill], 9
    - [Two men posing with a fence], 10
    - [ Young man and two young women sitting on a rocky hillside], 11
    - [Group of people with a snowey landscape behind them], 12
    - [Young man with a cane posing in fornt of a bush], 13
    - [Young man and woman sitting on a bridge], 14
    - This is my pal Charles P. Jamerson who married my Valpo girl, Esther Anderson [ signed photograph: Fraternally, Chas P Jamerson], 15
    - Note: This is my pal Charles P. Jamerson who married my Valpo girl, Esther Anderson [ signed photograph: Fraternally, Chas P Jamerson], 16
    - Fran's high school boy friend, his name was Wells, a really fine guy, 17
    - Note: Fran's high school boy friend, his name was Wells, a really fine guy, 18
    - This is Mr. Segard one of my best friends. He's a graduate of Columbia and the brightest boy I ever met. He takes a very active part in school and also leads the choir at the Christian church. His home is in San Francisco. He was captain of a submarine in the U.S. Navy for two yrs. and is only 25 yrs old, 19
    - Verso: This is Mr. Segard one of my best friends. He's a graduate of Columbia and the brightest boy I ever met. He takes a very active part in school and also leads the choir at the Christian church. His home is in San Francisco. He was captain of a submarine in the U.S. Navy for two yrs. and is only 25 yrs old, 19-verso
    - Dr. C. P. Segard, 20
    - Verso: Dr. C. P. Segard, 20-verso
    - [Two young men, one holding the other up both laughing], 21
    - [Young man smiling], 22
    - [Young woman], 23
    - [Group of people in font of a home], 24
    - [Group of young men in front of a mine (?)], 25
    - [View of a mountain], 26
    - [Group of young men in front of a mine (?)], 27
    - [Group of men helping each other over a fence], 28
  - Lowell Thomas: Funeral, 1981 September 3; 9 (Box 1524)
    - [People gathered at Lowell Thomas funeral], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. talking with Marianna Munn Thomas and other woman at Lowell Thomas's Funeral], 2
    - [Framed photo of Lowell Thomas over coffin], 3
    - [Line of people outside of funeral home(?)], 4
    - [Pall bearers loading a coffin into a hearse], 5
    - [Hearse outside of a church], 6
    - [Pall Bearers with coffin], 7
    - [Group of people outside of a church], 8
    - [Marianna Munn Thomas and two women in front of a photo of Lowell Thomas], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. talking with Marianna Munn Thomas and other woman at Lowell Thomas's Funeral], 10
  - Lowell Thomas: Honorary degrees, circa 1950s; 10 (Box 1524)
    - [Lowell Thomas in a cap and gown, with a cane] 2/14/53, 1
    - Verso: 2/14/53, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas in a cap and gown with another man in a cap and gown], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas at a CBS podium with people in caps and gowns], 3
  - Lowell Thomas: Honors, circa 1940; 11 (Box 1524)
    - Walter Pew of Sun Oil - a 10th anniv. [anniversary] presentation, 1
    - Verso: Walter Pew of Sun Oil - a 10th anniv. [anniversary] presentation, 1-verso
    - Niles Trammell, President of National Broadcasting Co., presenting "a gold-plated microphone to Lowell Thomas in recognition of his 10th anniversary as commentator with NBC. Thomas was honored at a party attended by fellow news-commentators at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel in New York City. Today, September 29 [1940]", 2
    - Note: Niles Trammell, President of National Broadcasting Co., presenting "a gold-plated microphone to Lowell Thomas in recognition of his 10th anniversary as commentator with NBC. Thomas was honored at a party attended by fellow news-commentators at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel in New York City. Today, September 29 [1940]", 3
    - 15.1 Photograph in LT 10 Year on the Air Anniversary of Niles Trammell presenting "a gold-plated microphone to Lowell Thomas in recogniton of his 10th anniversary as a commentator with N.B.C. Thomas was honored at a party attended by fellow news-commentators at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, Today, September 29 [1940]." International News Photo, 4
    - Note: 15.1 Photograph in LT 10 Year on the Air Anniversary of Niles Trammell presenting "a gold-plated microphone to Lowell Thomas in recogniton of his 10th anniversary as a commentator with N.B.C. Thomas was honored at a party attended by fellow news-commentators at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, Today, September 29 [1940]." International News Photo, 5
    - 15.1 Photograph in LT 10 Year on the Air Anniversary of Niles Trammell presenting "a gold-plated microphone to Lowell Thomas in recogniton of his 10th anniversary as a commentator with N.B.C. Thomas was honored at a party attended by fellow news-commentators at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, Today, September 29 [1940]." International News Photo, 6
    - [Lowell Thomas holding an award], 7
  - Lowell Thomas: Honors, circa 1930s - 1976; 12 (Box 1524)
    - Photograph by Newspictures, Inc. Note: The Splendid American Award presented annually by the Thomas A. Dooley Foundation, the Splendid American Award honors those Americans whose personal accomplishments have well reflected the meaning and purpose of the United States to the world community. The award was established in 1964 by the authors of "The Ugly American," William J. Lederer and the late Eugene Burdick. Mr. Burdick was President of the Dooley Foundation from 1961 until his death in 1965. Mr. Lederer each year presents the awards., 1
    - Note: Photograph by Newspictures, Inc. Note: The Splendid American Award presented annually by the Thomas A. Dooley Foundation, the Splendid American Award honors those Americans whose personal accomplishments have well reflected the meaning and purpose of the United States to the world community. The award was established in 1964 by the authors of "The Ugly American," William J. Lederer and the late Eugene Burdick. Mr. Burdick was President of the Dooley Foundation from 1961 until his death in 1965. Mr. Lederer each year presents the awards., 2
    - [Lowell Thomas holding an award with two men], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a plaque with three other men], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas in center holding awards with a group of men], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas on the right with two other men holding plaques], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas approaching podium, people clapping], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas approaching podium, people clapping], 8
    - IAHF Investiture 2 Oct 76 Balchen Award L-R John Rose, Gen Merkling, Audrey Balchen, 9
    - Verso: IAHF Investiture 2 Oct 76 Balchen Award L-R John Rose, Gen Merkling, Audrey Balchen, 9-verso
    - Lowell speaks at IAHF Investiture, San Diego, 2 Oct 1976; Councilman Jin Ellis presents San Diego Citation, 2 Oct 1976, 10
    - Verso: Lowell speaks at IAHF Investiture, San Diego, 2 Oct 1976; Councilman Jin Ellis presents San Diego Citation, 2 Oct 1976, 10-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a plague with another man], 11
    - [Lowell Thomsa at the front of a room with a group of men], 12
    - Letter to L.T. from Paul F. Hartz: Dear Lowell, Just revieved a pleasant reminder of the nice evening we had at the Explorer's Club in November of last year in the form of a new photographs.; If by chance you keep a scrapbook, I thought you might be interested in having the attached photograph.; Warmest regards, Sincerely, [signed] Paul F Hartz, 13
    - Note: Letter to L.T. from Paul F. Hartz: Dear Lowell, Just revieved a pleasant reminder of the nice evening we had at the Explorer's Club in November of last year in the form of a new photographs.; If by chance you keep a scrapbook, I thought you might be interested in having the attached photograph.; Warmest regards, Sincerely, [signed] Paul F Hartz, 14
    - [Governor's Award, 1976, Ohio], 15
    - Note: Letter to L.T. from Paul J. Sherlock: Dear Mr. Thomas: We regret the delay in sending you pictures of the Governor's Awards presentation ceremonies. Our one staff photographs has been so swamped with assignments that he couldn't get around to processing the film until now.; At any rate, we hope that the enclosed pictures will bring back pleasant memories of the evening's activities when Ohio's highest token of appreciation, the Governor's Award, was presented to you in recognition of your achievements benefiting mankind and for bringing honor and prestige to the Buckeye State.; Sincerely, [signed] Pauk J. Sherlock, Governor's Awards Coordinator, 16
    - 7/7/76 Governor's Island Presentation of Scrolls to new members. From left to right: George Sanborn, George Gettemuller, Clarence O'Connor, Elwyn Chesley, Joseph Conlin [The Circumnavigators Club], 17
    - Note: 7/7/76 Governor's Island Presentation of Scrolls to new members. From left to right: George Sanborn, George Gettemuller, Clarence O'Connor, Elwyn Chesley, Joseph Conlin [The Circumnavigators Club], 18
    - 7/7/76 Governor's Island Presentation of Scrolls to new members. From left to right: George Sanborn, George Gettemuller, Clarence O'Connor, Elwyn Chesley, Joseph Conlin [The Circumnavigators Club], 19
    - Note: 7/7/76 Governor's Island Capt. John Martin of the ESMERALDA, 20
    - 7/7/76 Governor's Island Capt. Susumu Hashimoto of the NIPPON MARU presents picture [to Lowell Thomas], 21
    - Note: 7/7/76 Governor's Island Capt. Susumu Hashimoto of the NIPPON MARU presents picture [to Lowell Thomas], 22
    - [The Circumnavigators Club], 23
    - LT escorted to platform to receive Colo award; The Colorado Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1550 Lincoln St. Room 205, Denver, Colorado 80203, 24
    - Verso: LT escorted to platform to receive Colo award; The Colorado Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1550 Lincoln St. Room 205, Denver, Colorado 80203, 24-verso
    - LT dinner, Nov 1965 [Thomas Dewey seated], 25
    - Verso: LT dinner, Nov 1965, 25-verso
  - Lowell Thomas: Honors [color photographs], circa late 1970s; 13 (Box 1524)
    - [left to right: Jack Anderson, Lowell Thomas, Danny Kaye], 1
    - [Alexander Haig and Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas, center, Alexander Haig, right], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas, center, Dan Moore, right], 4
    - [Marianna Munn Thomas at right], 5
    - [left to right: Marianna Munn Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Ann Landers (Esther "Eppie" Pauline Friedman Lederer)], 6
    - [left to right: Eleonore A. Bednowicz Rickover, Hyman Rickover, Lowell Thomas], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas on right another man beside him], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas recevieng award from a priest (?) from the University of Detroit], 9
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas - horses, circa late 1930s - 1940s; 14 (Box 1524)
    - "WHAT'S THAT YOU SAY?" Lowell Thomas, famous NBC commentator, trying out a story on Montana, one of the horses on his farm home at Pawling, N.Y. Maybe the steed is getting ready for a horse laugh NBC Photo, 8/10/34 [3 copies], 1
    - Note: "WHAT'S THAT YOU SAY?" Lowell Thomas, famous NBC commentator, trying out a story on Montana, one of the horses on his farm home at Pawling, N.Y. Maybe the steed is getting ready for a horse laugh NBC Photo, 8/10/34, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas holding on to a horses' bridle], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas with two horses], 4
  - Lowell Thomas: Kirkman, Iowa, undated; 15 (Box 1524)
    - Kirkman, Iowa - 1895-6-7-8-9?, 1
    - Verso: Kirkman, Iowa - 1895-6-7-8-9?, 1-verso
    - [Four men on a bridge (?) Lowell Thomas at right (?)], 2
    - [Church], 3
    - [Interior with a cast iron stove], 4
    - [View of a street in a small town], 5
  - Lowell Thomas: Valparaiso University professors, circa 1909 - 1911; 16 (Box 1524)
    - Prof. Geo. D. Timmons, Chemistry - Valparaiso, 1
    - Verso: Prof. Geo. D. Timmons, Chemistry - Valparaiso, 1-verso
    - Prof. Williams, professor of English - Valparaiso Univ., 2
    - Verso: Prof. Williams, professor of English - Valparaiso Univ., 2-verso
    - [?] b. Brown - Valparaiso Univ., 3
    - Verso: [?] b. Brown - Valparaiso Univ., 3-verso
    - [?], Dean of Classical Dept. - Valparaiso, 4
    - Verso: [?], Dean of Classical Dept. - Valparaiso, 4-verso
    - [?] W. Neet, Dean, Dept. of Education - Valparaiso, 5
    - Verso: [?] W. Neet, Dean, Dept. of Education - Valparaiso, 5-verso
    - Oliver P. Kinsey, V.P. - Valparaiso University, 6
    - Verso: Oliver P. Kinsey, V.P. - Valparaiso University, 6-verso
    - Oliver P. Kinsey, V.P. - Valparaiso University, 7
  - Lowell Thomas: Woodington, Ohio, undated; 17 (Box 1524)
    - Lowell in front of our own home at Woodington, 1
    - Verso: Lowell in front of our own home at Woodington, 1-verso
    - Caption: House at Woodington, Ohio where LT was born, 2
  - Posed photographs [Lowell Thomas], circa 1920s - 1930s; 18 (Box 1524)
    - [Lowell Thomas looking over his shoulder], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas as a young man], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas as a young man], 4
  Box 1525
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover photograph], 1931 September 19; 1 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [10 copies], 1
    - Verso: newspaper clipping, 1-verso
  - Publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover photograph], 1931 September 19; 2 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [60 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover photograph], 1931 September 19; 3 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [39 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover photograph], 1931 September 19; 4 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [46 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 5 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [34 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 6 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [15 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 7 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [14 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 8 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [34 copies], 1
    - Verso: 2nd choice taken when at least 5 yrs. Younger that no.I; Lowell Thomas, 1-verso
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 9 (Box 1525)
    - [Publicity photographs] [10 copies], 1
  Box 1526
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 1 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photo] [10 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 2 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photo] [25 copies], 1
    - Verso: no. 3 - At least its about the right vintage, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with a cane, publicity photo] [4 copies], 2
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 3 (Box 1526)
    - L.T. at his desk in his N.Y. apartment [5 copies], 1
    - Verso: L.T. at his desk in his N.Y. apartment, 1-verso
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 4 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas writing at his desk, publicity photo] [7 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1930s; 5 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas reading a book in front of a window with a view of New York], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas examining a globe (?)], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas writing at a type writer], 3
  - Publicity photographs, 1942; 6 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas on a boat] [15 copies], 1
    - Verso: Tracy Arm, Alaska. Sawyer Glacier - 1942, 1-verso
    - Note: Tracy Arm, active glacier near Juneau, Alaska, 2
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1940s; 7 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas with papers in his hand] [18 copies], 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Courtesy of Explorer's Club. By Dr. O.S. Wightman, F.R.P.S., 1-verso
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1940s; 8 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at his desk with papers in his hand, holding his chin] [26 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1950s; 9 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas Headshot with "Here's to you, Tom!" and his autograph] [29 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1950s; 10 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas] [8 copies], 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas portrait at time of "High Adventure" series., 1-verso
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1950s; 11 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas, 1957], 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, 1957, 1-verso
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1950s; 12 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of a window with a view of Washington D.C. (?)] [5 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1950s; 13 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1950s; 14 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas waving his hat] [4 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [with hippopotamus head at The Explorers Club], circa 1950s; 15 (Box 1526)
    - [Lowell Thomas with hippopotamus head at The Explorers Club ] [36 copies], 1
  Box 1527
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Publicity photographs (Morocco), 1958; 1 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas standing in front of Morroccan buildings] [26 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1960s; 2 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas holding a magazine(?) at a desk in front of a map] [29 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1960s; 3 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas holding sunglasses] [19 copies], 1
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas looking out the window of a train], 2
  - Publicity photographs, circa 1970s; 4 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting, holding his glasses] [12 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 5 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [2 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 6 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [7 unsigned copies], 1
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [autographed copy], 2
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 7 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [3 unsigned copies], 1
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [autographed copy], 2
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [autographed copy], 3
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [autographed copy], 4
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 8 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [30 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 9 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at two NBC microphones] [18 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 10 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [13 copies], 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas in the early days of broadcasting, 1-verso
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 11 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at a NBC microphone] [24 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 12 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at a NBC microphone with a globe and telephones], 1
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas in front of a NBC micrphone], 2
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas in front of a NBC microphone, side view], 3
    - Publicity photograph: Lowell Thomas at the Clover Brook Studio [NBC microphone and dog on table], [3 copies], 4
    - Note: Lowell Thomas at the Clover Brook studio, 5
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at desk holding papers with NBC microphone and bookcase in background], 6
  - Publicity photographs [at the NBC radio microphone], circa 1930s; 13 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at desk with NBC microphone and typewriter in background, likely Clover Brook office], 1
  - Publicity photographs [at the CBS radio microphone], circa 1940s - 1950s; 14 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at desk in sweater, four men stand behind him], 1
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at desk in sweater], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas stands at CBS microphone] Jan 8 1951; Dear Lowell - Many thanks for letting me have a chance to make this shot of you for my album - Best, [signed] Dick Teely [Feely?], 3
    - Verso: Jan 8 1951; Dear Lowell - Many thanks for letting me have a chance to make this shot of you for my album - Best, [signed] Dick Teely [Feely?], 3-verso
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at desk with CBS microphone], [3 copies], 4
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at desk with CBS microphone], [signed copy], 5
  - Publicity photographs [at the CBS radio microphone], circa 1950s; 15 (Box 1527)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at desk with CBS microphone], [35 copies], 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, 1-verso
  Box 1528